<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Versiones</string>
    <string name="Beta">La beta ya está disponible de forma oficial, así que es cuestión de minutos que llegue a todos los dispositivos Google Pixel que ya tengan la beta instalada. No hay demasiados cambios, mayormente se arreglan algunos fallos de la anterior beta, pero sí hay elementos a destacar.</string>
    <string name="Cupcake">Android "Cupcake" (version 1.5) is the third version of Android developed by Google, a major platform release deployable to Android-powered handsets starting in April 2009, that is no longer supported. The release included new features for users and developers, as well as changes in the Android framework API. For developers, the Android 1.5 platform was available as a downloadable component for the Android SDK.</string>
    <string name="Donut">Android "Donut" is the fourth version of the open source Android mobile operating system developed by Google that is no longer supported. Among the more prominent features introduced with this update were added support for CDMA smartphones, additional screen sizes, a battery usage indicator, and a text-to-speech engine.[1]
After the public release of Donut—its official dessert-themed code name the convention employed by Google to designate major Android versions—carriers were quick to follow with its roll out to customers in the form of an over-the-air (OTA) update for compatible smartphones.</string>
    <string name="Eclair">Android "Eclair" is a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and the fifth operating system for Android, and for the no-longer supported versions 2.0 to 2.1. Unveiled on October 26, 2009, Android 2.1 builds upon the significant changes made in Android 1.6 "Donut".</string>
    <string name="Froyo">Android "Froyo" is the sixth version of Android and is a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 2.2 and 2.2.3.[1] Those versions are no longer supported. It was unveiled on May 20, 2010, during the Google I/O 2010 conference.</string>
    <string name="GinGer_Bread">Android "Gingerbread" is the seventh version of Android, a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and released in December 2010, for versions that are no longer supported. The Gingerbread release introduced support for near field communication (NFC)—used in mobile payment solutions—and Session Initiation Protocol (SIP)—used in VoIP internet telephones.</string>
    <string name="Honey_Comb">Android "Honeycomb" is the codename for the eighth version of Android, designed for devices with larger screen sizes, particularly tablets. It is no longer supported (newer versions are). Honeycomb debuted with the Motorola Xoom in February 2011.[2][3] Besides the addition of new features, Honeycomb introduced a new so-called "holographic" user interface theme and an interaction model that built on the main features of Android, such as multitasking, notifications and widgets.</string>
    <string name="Ice_Cream">Android "Ice Cream Sandwich" is the ninth version of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google. Unveiled on October 19, 2011, Android 4.0 builds upon the significant changes made by the tablet-only release Android Honeycomb, in an effort to create a unified platform for both smartphones and tablets.</string>
    <string name="Jelly_Bean">Android "Jelly Bean" is the tenth version of Android and the codename given to three major point releases of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 4.1 and 4.3.1. Some operating systems that run Android 4.3/4.4 are Asus Nexus 7 (2013).</string>
    <string name="KitKat">Android "KitKat" is a codename for the Android mobile operating system and the eleventh version of Android. Unveiled on September 3, 2013, KitKat focused primarily on optimizing the operating system for improved performance on entry-level devices with limited resources.</string>
</resources>